- [Senu] It's nice to meet you!
- The beastmen from
Howling Village moved here.
If you need anything,
just ask Lamulias here.
- It's very nice to meet you.
- Yes!
- You don't need
to be that formal.
Apparently they all thought
that they were going to be
treated horribly
when they moved here.
Naturally, we have
no such intentions.
- There appear to be no issues
with the new residents, but...
- [Hiraku] But?
[girls gasping]
- [Lamulias] They faint
quite often.
- [Hiraku] Well, they'll just
have to get used to things.
["Flower Ring" by Shino Shimoji
and Aya Suzaki plays]
[all laughing]
- Wait!
- Come and get us!
[magic whirring]
[boy gasping]
- Geez, you need to be
careful when you play.
- You can use magic too, Senu?
- Yes. Yes, I can.
- Don't tell me Tia, am I the
only one who can't use magic?
- Well, all of the angels
can use magic.
- And all the high elves
[water splashing]
- It is common for us
to be able to use
fire and water magic.
- We're good with using
magic for water.
[fire roaring]
[Hiraku clapping]
- Even the bees can do it.
[fire roaring]
- Don't worry, mayor!
There are others with no magic.
- Hey, let's practice
together, mayor.
- Yeah, you're right.
I have a feeling these
kids will surpass me.
Oh well, there's no point in
wishing for the impossible.
I'll just focus on
what I can do for now.
[ground rumbling]
What was That? An earthquake?
- Mayor!
A grappler bear
and a bloody viper
are fighting in the forest!
- Bear and viper.
A bear and a snake?
[ground rumbling]
[both grunting]
Those two fighting each other is
enough to make the ground shake?
- What should we do?
- A bear and a viper.
- If this continues,
it might affect the village,
but I fear it would be dangerous
to get involved without a plan.
- Yeah, that's true.
So those animals, do you
think we can eat them?
[Granmaria gasps]
So anyways,
I've heard that hunters
sometimes eat bear meat.
I've always wondered how
bear meat would taste.
- Right.
Down there. Look.
[dramatic music]
[beasts growling]
- [Hiraku] Whoa!
They're big.
- We should go back for help.
- No, just take me down
really fast.
[Granmaria gasps]
- I understand.
[dramatic music continues]
[Hiraku grunts]
[sword slicing]
[ground rumbling]
- Haven't had a big one
in a while.
- [Lizardmen] One, two!
- What's wrong?
- You think you
could take down
a monster like that
with one attack?
- No way.
- That's crazy.
The mayor is something else.
- Wow.
Looking at him up close,
he really is huge.
- As far as cooking
the bear goes,
what do you plan to make?
- Got an idea.
[fire crackling]
[light music]
I'll add some of these
herbs and spices.
Now we add wine and simmer.
- [Both] Our delicious,
precious wine?
- [Hiraku] It's fine.
That kind of cooking is normal.
And there we have it;
wine braised grappler bear.
[both gasping]
[Hiraku chewing]
It's incredibly gamey.
- [Both] Our delicious,
precious wine.
- I'm telling you,
this is normal.
And this is the blood viper.
I tried frying it.
[Hiraku humming]
That tastes just like
fried chicken!
- It's delicious!
- It tastes different
than I thought.
- [Hiraku] It tastes
surprisingly like
chicken breast,
which means my plate
is missing something
that goes right here.
- So then, what brings
you here today?
- Perhaps, do you have
an antibacterial agent?
- Antibacterial?
- Yeah.
I need to use it for a new
recipe I want to try out.
Do you have any medicines that
can kill harmful microorganisms?
- Microorganisms?
Those are the things
you spoke of before!
- Yeah, that's them.
I want something that will
prevent stomach aches
or illness.
- I see!
Just leave it to me.
How about this one here?
One dose will blast anything to
the other side of the mountains.
- [Hiraku] Do you have
anything more peaceful?
- Then how about this one?
This one is safe enough
to use in foods.
- Yeah, this'll work.
Thanks.
- Of course.
- By the way, how's the
miso production coming?
[Flora groans]
- The honest truth is
not very well.
I did everything exactly
like you told me to,
but no matter how long I waited,
it never started to ferment.
[loud explosion]
I've had to rebuild
my hut three times.
- That's not supposed to happen!
Well, let's give it
another try then.
- Really?
I'll keep the explosives
to a minimum.
- Please don't use any.
[rooster crowing]
[chickens clucking]
Yes! Perfect!
[egg cracking]
First, we gently beat the eggs.
Add salt and vinegar.
This vinegar is made
from apples.
- That's also fermented, right?
[Hiraku laughs]
- Then we mix it as we
slowly add in the oil.
And now we have mayonnaise.
- Oh!
- Now it's exactly like
having fried chicken.
- Oh, wow!
I could eat this by itself
without food.
- Stop that right now!
It's terrible for your health!
Now then, onto making miso.
First, we start by simmering
the soybeans we soaked in water.
Then we grind them.
[Flora humming]
[magic whirring]
Moldy, moldy, moldy.
I used the almighty farming tool
to help make the koji mold.
You don't need to
write that down.
We mixed the koji with
salt and form balls.
Now we pack it into barrels.
- Oh, I see.
Mine didn't work because
I didn't say "moldy-mold."
- [Hiraku] No, that's,
well, maybe.
Now we just let it
age in the cellar.
It'll take a few months,
so let's wait patiently.
- [Flora] That long?
- Yeah.
But all that time will make
the flavors even more intense.
- This requires perseverance
just like research.
- Right!
- Ah!
There you are.
You've got visitors.
- Visitors?
The visitors were
a group of dwarves
led by a man named Donovan.
- We are elder dwarves.
- [Hiraku] What's the
difference?
- We've heard that you have
high quality alcohol
in this village and we'd
like you to share some.
- Do you mean our wine?
I'd be happy to share some.
- Mayor Hiraku, I'm afraid we
can't give it away for free.
- Huh?
- She's right.
Our wine is very valuable.
- I know, but they're
our guests here.
- I'm sorry, but we
don't have any money.
However, we do have technology.
- Technology?
- That's right.
We've spent our lives
studying alcohol production
and we've traveled
a long way to get here.
You have some very fine
crops in this village.
We can help you turn them
into fine alcohol.
What do you think?
Don't you want to drink some?
[all gasping]
- [Hiraku] Donovan and
his men got to work
on the alcohol right away.
Distillation.
I remember doing this
in science class.
[alcohol drips]
- Here you go!
This is corn whiskey.
- It's crystal clear!
- It'll get its color when
we age it in the barrels.
- Oh, I see.
[Hiraku groans]
This is really strong!
[Donovan laughing]
- I guess the mayor's
a bit of a lightweight.
- Donovan and his men ended up
staying in the village
and working as our brewers.
Now that we've got new alcohol,
it's time to have
a welcome party
for the beastmen
and the dwarfs!
Drink up, everyone!
[all cheering]
[tavern music]
- You can really taste
all the fragrance that went
into this alcohol
when you give it a sip.
- I really like this mayonnaise!
- This goes perfect
with the booze.
- Let's drink all night,
everyone!
- He snuck in again.
- I don't mind that
he comes here,
but he always drinks
way too much of our wine.
- Right, it's time to
show you all my special
one-of-a-kind technique.
[Dryme snoring]
[Hiraku chuckling]
- Thanks for everything, mayor.
It was very kind of you
to take us all in.
- Don't mention it.
We're all happy you're here.
- Yeah!
There are a lot of people
in this village
who like to drink.
- Wait a minute,
I finally got some adult men
to join the village.
By the way, Donovan,
I'm not asking for any
particular reason,
but are there any girls here
who catch your eye?
You know, that kind that
make you think,
"Wow, she's pretty!"
- Well, I can certainly say
that they're all very
good looking and all,
but you know,
I think they're just a bit
too young for me.
If they can't at least
grow a beard,
then they're not for me.
- [Hiraku] A beard?
- Man, why are you making me
say it out loud like that?
- The cultural barrier is high.
[Hiraku hiccups]
Farming Life...
- [Senu] In Another...
- [Hiraku] World.
[dragon whooshing]
[horn blowing]
[dramatic music]
Don't tell me there's
another wyvern.
Wait, a dragon?
It's headed straight for us!
It doesn't look friendly.
I'm going to
finish this one off
before it causes any
damage to the village.
[dragon crashing]
What just happened?
Isn't that Dryme?
Is this infighting?
But they're just
staring each other down.
There's another one!
[dragon roaring]
That one's dangerous.
[Hiraku grunts]
[spear whooshing]
I missed!
[spear zaps]
But the next one won't.
- Please, wait, mayor!
That isn't an enemy
to the village!
[Hiraku groans]
I'm terribly sorry
for the confusion.
These two are my
master's beloved wife
and his precious daughter.
- My name is Lastismoon.
- I'm Graffaloon,
nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Hiraku Machio.
Why are your wife
and daughter here?
- Well, you see.
- Apparently Dryme's constant
sneaking out so that he could
come to our village has roused
some suspicion at home.
- [Lastismoon] What were we
supposed to think when he was
sneaking out every night?
- [Graffaloon] If it turned out
he was sneaking out
to do something he shouldn't.
[Dryme laughing]
- What an utterly
ridiculous accusation.
- But you were sneaking off
with all kinds of stuff
from the treasury.
- And not coming home
till the morning.
- Oh, I get it now.
It's the gifts he's
always bringing us.
And I was worried about him
going home drunk,
so I built him a house.
Maybe that wasn't
such a good idea.
- That was for the sake of
our diplomatic relations.
It was all very high
level politics-
- He's hiding something, mother.
- Yes.
At this point,
my suspicions are
all being confirmed.
- [Hiraku] She's scary.
- Wait a minute, you two!
Just think about it.
Don't you think this man
actually has the courage
to have an affair like that?!
- That's a good point.
[chimes ringing]
- Oh, thank goodness.
- Are you all happy with that?
Excuse me.
Even though I don't know you,
I'm sorry about earlier.
- No, no, no!
Don't worry about it!
This was all our fault.
Come on, you two,
apologize to the mayor!
- I'm sorry I tried to
burn the village down
because I thought my dad
was having an affair.
- And I'm sorry that I was
about to obliterate
the insolent man who pointed
a spear at my dear daughter.
- [Hiraku] They're scary!
- Well then, I guess
everything settled now.
- But dear husband, you
still shouldn't sneak out
to get drunk like that.
- What are you saying?
- [Lastismoon] She said,
you still shouldn't sneak out
to get drunk like that.
- Well, I'm just glad to see
that they're getting along.
Okay, see you all later.
- Yes.
Do you see what I was doing?
- Our continued relationship
with this village
is of the utmost importance.
- Despite their lack of numbers,
they still possess the power
necessary to challenge us.
I never thought
we'd meet anyone
that had the strength
to overwhelm us.
- Yeah, you're right.
You couldn't even defend
against that attack,
you had to avoid it.
- [Graffaloon] Even that was
only thanks to the spider.
- [Lamulias] Spider?
- Yes, an old friend of mine.
Had I not been pulled
out of the way,
I may not be standing
here with you now.
Lasti.
- Yes?
- I have a very important
job for you to do.
I want you to live here
for a while.
- Oh!
Mother, why?
- Why would you do that?
- This is a good chance
for you to be quiet.
- Yes, dear.
- We can't ignore
that kind of power.
I don't expect you to be
able to suppress it.
I just expect you
to do your duty
and make sure that such power
is not turned on us.
Is that understood?
- Yes. I will do my best.
- Is that wise?
- Yes. I believe that
choosing this path
will lead to the best
outcome for Lasti.
I can feel it within me.
- Sure.
I don't mind if she stays.
- I look forward to
working here!
If you wouldn't mind,
please call me Lasti.
- Sure. Sounds good.
- So then, what do you
want me to do?
- And like that,
Lasti immediately went
to work in the village.
- I'm ready to start now!
- Uh, are you a dragon creature?
- [Hiraku] However.
[tomato splats]
[Senu whimpers]
- What the?
[Lastismoon humming]
- [Hiraku] Dragons are pretty
extraordinary in all regards.
- Gently.
Gently.
[Lastismoon sneezes]
[apples explodes]
- [Hiraku] It looks like
it'll take a while
for her to get used to her work.
[boy laughing]
- Wait up!
- [Hiraku] What should we
do with her?
- [Tia] You don't need to
make her do something
she isn't a fit for.
- But Dryme really
wanted to give her
some work to do
around here.
[wolf whimpering]
What is it?
- They've been acting like this
ever since the dragons
showed up in the village.
The cows and chickens have
been acting scared too.
We haven't been able to
get any milk or eggs.
[Hiraku sighs]
- Dryme acts like that,
so I wasn't really
thinking about it,
but everyone is normally
afraid of dragons, aren't they?
- It's not just the power
they have either.
Their knowledge and
wisdom is also great.
- In that case.
- [Lastismoon] Sorry to
keep you waiting.
- Don't worry about.
[Beezel grunting]
- I'm Lastismoon,
and I'm in charge of handling
diplomatic relations
here at the village.
- Don't tell me you are
that dragon girl.
- I am.
Please call me Lasti.
What is it that you've come
to request from us today?
[Beezel whimpers]
- We'd like to get
more of those
bright colored fruit
we got last time.
- You mean the oranges, right?
I'm sorry to say our stock
is running quite low.
Could I interest you in
strawberries instead?
They're perfectly ripe now.
- In that case, I'll take
10 boxes of those, please.
- Wow! Thank you so much!
Could I interest you in
some apples and pears
to go with them?
We have persimmons
and watermelons too.
- Okay, I'll take those.
- [Lastismoon]
Here's your order.
- Thank you very much.
- Would you like to
count them to confirm?
- That won't be necessary!
- [Lastismoon]
Very well.
We look forward to
seeing you again.
- It looks like she's got
the hang of this.
- What?!
They have dragons now?!
This is a joke!
- That village's military
might grows by the day.
- We need to monitor them.
Should we send a spy
there to the village?
- If they find out,
it'll be an act of aggression!
[Beezel sighs]
- We have no other choice.
I have a plan.
[door clicking]
- Pardon me, Father.
I understand you called for me.
- Yes.
Flowrem, please have a seat.
- I see.
You want me to investigate
that Great Tree Village?
- Yes.
In particular,
their military might.
However, you mustn't do
anything rash.
Your safety must always be
your number one concern.
- Understood.
But Father, I am
your daughter, after all.
I'm confident in my magic,
so don't worry.
[Beezel sighs]
[Flowrem zipping]
Oh.
At a glance, this seems
like an ordinary village,
but how did they develop a
village like this in the middle
of a forest filled with such
terrifying monsters?
- Welcome to the
Great Tree Village!
I'm Lastismoon, head of
diplomatic relations.
- It's nice to meet you.
- You're going to stay here in
this village for a while, right?
I heard from Beezel.
You can call me Lasti.
- Isn't Lastismoon
that infamous dragon
that everyone is afraid of?
I can't believe I've already
met someone this powerful.
- Are you okay?
I'm going to show you
around the village.
- Oh! Okay!
- And this here
is our vineyard.
We can make delicious wine
from these grapes here.
My father said that
the wine here is the most-
- It seems like just
an ordinary vineyard.
- Roar!
- [Flowrem] Why is a legendary
dragon in a place like this
bragging to me about
crops they're growing?
- And get this, so then
my dad told me that- Oh.
- I'm sorry to interrupt.
I've spotted a messenger
from Howling Village.
- Oh! Okay, thank you!
Sorry, I need to go and take
care of something for a second.
- Don't you worry about it.
I can look around on my own.
- Okay. See you later.
- This works out perfectly.
I can take the opportunity to
analyze their military strength.
Those are lizardmen.
Beastmen and ogres.
And even dwarves.
They'll all be
tough to deal with,
but with the full force
of our military,
we should be able
to handle them.
This might be their
headquarters.
The Vampire Princess!
I heard she was on the run
from Nobles,
so she was laying low.
What's she doing here?
The Angel of Annihilation, Tia.
Why is she in the same
village as Lulucy ?
And I'm pretty sure I heard
that those three are called
the Trio of Killer Angels.
They even have high elves here?
I've heard that those
are terrifying man eaters
that prey upon helpless
young men and kidnap them.
If there are five here,
then this is already
too much for our military.
Impossible!
And they have inferno wolves
and demon spiders,
and they formed a pack?!
Up until now, I've been proud to
call myself one of the most
talented magic users in all of
the Demonic Kingdom, but
I feel like all my confidence
has left me.
To command all of these
powerful troops,
it would make sense to
assume that Lastismoon
was in charge of such
an organization.
But there's someone above
her called the Mayor
who rules over all of them.
What kind of terrifying
opponent am I dealing with?
Huh?
- Huh?
- It's just a human?
Why is a human
here of all places?
- What are you doing out here?
Are you lost or something?
- Don't worry about me.
I'm not so weak that
I need an ordinary human
to worry about me.
What? That person
I saw just now?
- Yep. That's the mayor
of our village.
- But isn't he just
an ordinary human?
- He's a human strong enough
to defeat my mom if he wants.
- That just can't be!
- [Lastismoon]
Did you say hello?
- Forget saying hello,
I was outright rude to him.
There we go.
[bright music]
- I found out that girl
was Beezel's daughter.
Apparently she's going to
live here for a while.
She seems to be getting
along well with Lasti.
That's great and all, but...
- Good morning, mayor!
- Good morning.
- I hope you have
a lovely day.
- For some reason she acted
like this for a while.
["Feel the winds"
by Yui Hizuki plays]
[rustic music playing]